<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Emotion on Kelly&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>http://kkyinli.github.io/notes/categories/emotion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Emotion on Kelly&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kkyinli.github.io/notes/categories/emotion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CONCENTRATION</title>
      <link>http://kkyinli.github.io/notes/post/concentration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kkyinli.github.io/notes/post/concentration/</guid>
      <description>The holiday will be over soon.
I did some things unplaned.
And some things which had to be done was not done.
Anything, as long as you concentrate on doing it, you may be able to do the utmost.
I believe it. No matter how small this thing is.
But in most cases, we lack focus and persistence. Therefore, we became a common person.
In our whole limited life, Even if we do one thing, it is already very great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABOUT ANXIETY</title>
      <link>http://kkyinli.github.io/notes/post/about-anxiety/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kkyinli.github.io/notes/post/about-anxiety/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think it a good sigh for my recently dysphoric. I can&amp;rsquo;t figure out the reason. But I feel the pressure. I dislike it. But I can&amp;rsquo;t expel them.
So I try to figure out what happened to me recently?
What caused my anxiety?
What makes me worried?
How could I solve them?
Xiaobo Wang had said, the origin of pain comes from the scarce capacity. I did.
So, the best way to conquer this unpleasant emotion is to empower myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OUT OF MIND</title>
      <link>http://kkyinli.github.io/notes/post/out-of-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kkyinli.github.io/notes/post/out-of-mind/</guid>
      <description>Many different kinds of thoughts came in my mind which gave rise to my absent-mindedness.
Recently, some books and movies touched my soul. Who I am? Where should I go to? What&amp;rsquo;s the mean of life? Many things are waiting for me. I know I must solve them.
Though many theories tortured me, the positive blueprint about future is clear than ever. All roads lead to Roma and I know where is Roma.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>